My
>> like I say, welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
where we open up with the ten
commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep. Brother James.
>> Yes, sir. And God spake all these words,
saying, I am the Lord thy God, which
have brought thee out of the land of
Egypt, out of the house of bondage. Thou
shalt have no other gods before me. Thou
shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in the
earth beneath, or that is in the water
under the earth. Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I
the Lord thy God am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day, to
keep it holy. Sixth day shalt thou labor
and do all thy work, but the seventh day
is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In
it thou shalt not do any work, thou, nor
thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in them is, and rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hallowed it. Honor thy father
and thy mother, that thy days may be
long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee. Thou shalt not kill.
Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou
shalt not steal. Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor. Thou
shalt not covet thy neighbor's house.
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's
wife, nor as man's servant, nor his
maid's servant, nor his ox, nor his ass,
nor anything that is thy neighbors. I
read Exodus ver Exodus 20:es 1-1 17. May
the Lord add a blessing to the reading
of his word. In Jesus name we pray.
Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. So here on question and answer,
you can ask us a question and we'll
answer it according to the King James
Bible. And if we cannot find the answer,
we will seek further counsel to bring
you an answer at a later time. The
questions we will not answer are the
vague as well as the long scripture
questions and questions of debate. We
are not here to debate. We are here to
spread the true gospel of Jesus. So,
please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible. No other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program. Also, keep in mind this is a
live stream, so feel free to send in
your questions that pertain to
everlasting life. We just ask that you
keep them to a two scripture maximum.
But let me introduce to you the family
that's on the panel this evening. We got
Brother Dre. Good evening,
>> brother Julius.
>> Good evening, everybody.
>> Brother Jerome, grace and peace,
>> brother James.
>> Good evening, everyone.
>> Sister Deborah,
>> good evening.
>> Brother Sean,
>> And we have the guest caller with us.
And I'm brother Cornell. Sister Deborah,
what is our first question?
Uh yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A. So K
with P asks, "Was Mary filled with an
angel and Luke 1 verse41 is given."
>> All right. Mary was filled with the word
of God. We just had a three-part series
lesson on that and it was a lot that you
could have gleaned from those three
lessons. But let's go into you got here
Luke 1 and 41. Let's go there. Luke 1
and 41
because you ask was she was Mary filled
with an angel?
She was filled with the word of God. And
also the son of God, which is Jesus, was
in the same room as she was in and her
babe leaped. Go ahead, brother. And it
came to pass that when Elizabeth heard
the salutation of Mary, the babe leaped
in her womb, and Elizabeth was filled
with the Holy Ghost.
>> All right. So, the babe leaped in her
room, in her womb, and Elizabeth was
filled with the Holy Ghost. Read a
little more. And she spake out with a
loud voice and said, "Blessed art thou
among women, and blessed is the fruit of
thy womb."
>> Next verse.
>> And when it And whence is this to me
that the mother of my Lord should come
to me?
>> Mhm.
>> For lo, as soon as the voice of thy
salutation sounded in mine ears, the
babe leaped in my womb for joy.
>> Yep. One more verse. And blessed is she
that believed, for there shall be a
performance of those things which were
told of her from the Lord.
>> which were told of her from the Lord.
And let's go back and let's see what it
was that Elizabeth because this is
Elizabeth we reading about here. But you
said Mary in 41, but this is Elizabeth.
Turn back, brother, and just pick it up
at that verse 11. And let's see what uh
Elizabeth knew. Go ahead.
>> And there appeared unto him an angel of
the Lord standing on the right side of
the altar of incense. And when Zacharias
>> And when Zachcharias saw him, he was
troubled, and fear fell upon him. But
the angel said unto him, "Fear not,
Zachcharias, for thy prayer is heard,
and thy wife Elizabeth shall bear thee a
son, and thou shalt call his name John."
>> Yes. And thou shalt have joy and
gladness, and many shall rejoice at his
birth.
>> For he shall be great in the sight of
the Lord, and shall drink neither wine
nor strong drink, and he shall be filled
with the Holy Ghost, even from his
mother's womb.
>> Yes. And this is what Elizabeth knew
also, that she was going to have a child
in her old age, John, which was to pave
the way before Jesus, which you can pick
up in that verse. um 28 seeing where the
angel came unto Mary and gave her the
word of God also. So this was the word
of God that was in these two sisters
that knew that um Elizabeth would be
given birth to a son and name him John
who was going to be great and came
before Jesus. And then Mary was carrying
Jesus which was also receiving the
message by an angel just like Zachariah
did. That's all I got.
All right, we're gonna leave it right
there and we're going to go on to our
next question.
>> Next question. Michelle from Louisiana
asks in numbers 21 verse14,
the book of the war of the Lord. Is that
available to be purchased? And if so,
which one is IOG approved for accuracy
of truth?
All right, the book of the wars.
Reverend Julius,
>> first of all, uh, good evening
everybody.
That book does not exist because you got
it in your you got it in your hands.
The book of the wars of the Lord are the
battles that from Genesis to Revelation.
Let me show you what I'm talking about.
Let's go to 2 Chronicles the 2 chapter.
Well, let's read 20 uh numbers 21 and
read verse uh 13 and 14.
>> Okay. From then they removed and pitched
on the other side of Arnon, which is in
the wilderness that cometh out of the
coast of the Amorites.
>> The coast of the what?
>> The Amorites.
>> Big giant tall people. Hammites. Go
ahead.
>> For Arnon is the border of Moab between
Moab and the Amorites.
>> Go ahead.
Wherefore it is said in the book of the
wars of the Lord what he did in the Red
Sea and in the
>> wait a minute what he did in the Red
Sea. Where can I read what the Lord did
in the Red Sea? In the book of Exodus
the 14th chapter. I don't need the book
of the wars of the Lord because it is
written in the Bible. Continue.
>> What he did in the Red Sea and in the
brooks of Arna.
>> What did he do in the brooks of Arnon?
He destroyed the Amorites. It is written
in the book of Deuteronomy. These big
tall giant people when the Lord was uh
building up Israel and conquering all
the nations.
So now wherefore it is said in the book
of the wars of the Lord what he did in
the Red Sea and what he did in the books
of Aron. Now let's go to 2 Chronicles
chapter 2.
>> I look at this in all my years. I have
never read a book of a single book of
the book of the wars of the Lord. It is
mentioned in the all through the Bible.
The battle of Armageddon will be a war
of the Lord. The the the wrath of the
Lord, that's when the Lord fight against
these nation that persecutes Israel.
Continue. 2 Chronicles 2 and read verse
15. 2 Chronicles 2 and let me see. This
is 2 Chronicles 2 and verse 15.
Uh, that's not what I'm looking for.
That is not what I'm looking for.
Go to I'm sorry, 1st Samuel 17. 1st
Samuel 17, James.
>> 1 Samuel.
Okay. 1st Samuel 17
>> and read verse 47. Pay attention to what
we're reading.
>> And all this assembly shall know that
the Lord saveth not with sword and
spear. For the battle is the Lord's and
he will give you into our hands.
>> So now the battle is the Lord's. All of
these are the Lord's battles that he
fight for Israel. So therefore we can
read it also in 2 Chronicles where he
said the again it is quoted another
place the battle is the Lord's. He said
you ain't got to go up and fight. This
fight is not yours but this fight is the
battle of the Lord's. So the Israel of
God, I've never seen a copy of the book
of the wars of the Lord because it
doesn't exist.
So the Bible, the Bible, all 66 books is
called the book of the Lord. Isaiah
34:16 says you to seek ye out of the
book of the Lord. But book is biblos,
a combination of writings. We got 66
books which all contain in one book. So
now when you read the wars of the book
of the lords, read first kings, 2 kings,
read the whole bible, Genesis and Exodus
where he fought against Egypt and
Pharaoh. All of these are the books of
the wars of the Lord. Anybody want to
add to that?
>> All right. And also, brother Julius, we
do have a a lesson available called the
last three battles, too, which can
further educate them on more of the
battles of the Lord. So my sister
Michelle from Louisiana, don't waste
your time. Don't waste your money. Read
the Bible and you will run into all the
wars of the Lord that he fought for
Israel and even against Israel.
>> But all of these are the books of the
wars of the Lord from Genesis to
Revelation. That's all I got.
>> All right, I'm going to leave it there.
Hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one. Moving on. Sam
Burns says, "I see in Exodus 23:14
and Deuteronomy 16:E16,
God speaks of the men coming before him
to the feast three times in the year.
Does this still apply today? And does it
apply only to Israel?"
>> Does it still apply today or is it only
to Israel? Brother Jerome.
>> Um, yeah, it it still apply today. Um,
but it don't just apply to Israel. You
know, the Lord want all the nations to
keep these feasts even until this day.
And he want you to bring all your
family. You know, uh, but uh, when you
let's go read those verses that you gave
though. Exodus 23
verse 14.
When you get it, go ahead.
Three times thou shalt keep a feast unto
me in the year. Thou shalt keep the
feast of unleaven bread. Thou shalt eat
unleaven bread seven days as I command
thee in the time appointed of the on the
month Aib. For in it thou camest out of
Egypt, and none shall appear before me
empty.
And uh Deuteronomy 16:16,
>> three times a in a year shall all thy
males appear before the Lord thy God in
the place which he shall choose in the
feast of unleaven bread and in the feast
of weeks and in the feast of
tabernacles. And they shall not appear
before the Lord empty.
>> Yeah. See, Israel are a priest nation.
So as when the Lord teach Israel what we
must do then Israel job is to teach all
the rest of the sons of Adam so we can
be one one body
you know walking in the same spirit and
word of God. Okay. But uh even in the
book of acts after Jesus uh had died and
ascended back into heaven you can read
sometime later where uh apostle Paul
continued to keep these feasts. Okay. So
let's go to acts the 18th chapter
and we're going to read verse 19- 21.
Okay. N uh Acts 18 19- 21 says, "And he
came to Ephesus and left them there. But
he himself entered into the synagogue
and reasoned with the Jews. When they
desired him to tarry longer time with
them, he consented not, but bathed them
farewell, saying, "I must by all means
keep this feast that cometh in
Jerusalem, but I will return again unto
you if God will." And he sailed from
Ephesus.
>> Yeah. because he realized just what we
had just read um in the uh Exodus 23
and4 Deuteronomy 16:16. So that's why he
said by all means I got to keep these
feasts that be in Jerusalem. Okay. So
let's go to uh Exodus 20. Read verse 16.
>> Okay. Exodus 20
and verse 16 says
Exodus 20 and verse 16.
>> Yes.
What did it say?
>> Thou shalt not bow.
>> I said Exodus.
>> Yeah, you did.
>> I meant Acts.
>> Okay.
>> Acts 20 verse 16.
>> Okay. Acts 20 and verse 16 says, "For
Paul had determined to sail by Ephesus
because he had he would not spend the
time in Asia for he hasted if it were
possible for him to be at Jerusalem the
day of Pentecost."
>> Yeah. And so that's one of those three
feasts. So he was going to be keeping
Pentecost. He going to be keeping the
other two as well. All right. So even
when you go get into the future, even
beyond us, because we still supposed to
be keeping these feasts today, not not
just Israel, right? If you go to
Zechariah 14, it talks about how the
Lord had all the nations come. This is
after the Lord is back. And he said they
had to come up to keep the feast of
tabernacles.
That's in Zechariah the 14th chapter.
You can take uh read that uh when you
get a chance. That's all I got on it.
All right, thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question,
>> next question. Pauline R asked for you
to explain Matthew 12:31.
And she wants to know, is this the same
as the sin unto death in First John 5:1
16 and 17?
>> All right. Between the two verses, are
they the same? Brother Dre, what you
say?
Let's go read Matthew 12:31
and32.
>> James read verses 3132.
Matthew 12 31-32. Go ahead.
>> Wherefore I say unto you, all manner of
sin and blasphemy shall be forgiven unto
men, but the blasphemy against the Holy
Ghost shall not be forgiven unto men.
And whosoever speaketh a word against
the Son of Man, it shall be forgiven
him, but who whosoever speaketh against
the Holy Ghost, it shall not be forgiven
him, neither in this world, neither in
the world to come.
>> So you got to be very careful about
speaking against the word of God. But go
to first John the fifth chapter. 1 John
five and read verse
>> uh 16 and 17. First John 5 16 and 17. Go
ahead brother.
>> If any man see his brother sin a sin
which is not unto death, he shall ask
and he shall give him life for them that
sin, not unto death. There is a sin unto
death. I do not say that he shall pray
for it.
>> Right? So, yeah, speaking against the
word of God can get you in trouble. But
let's go to Exodus 23 and we going to
read verses 20 and 21. Exodus 23
20 and 21. Go ahead, brother, when you
get it.
>> Exodus 23 and what was the verse again?
>> 20 and 21.
>> Okay. Behold, I send an angel before
thee to keep thee in the way, and to
bring thee into the place which I have
prepared. Beware of him, and obey his
voice. Provoke him not, for he will not
pardon your transgressions, for my name
is in him." So this angel is coming in
the name of the Lord, speaking the word
of the Lord. And we are to beware and
obey his voice and provoke him not
because he will not pardon our
transgressions because his name is
the Lord's name is in him. Now one other
place real quick. John 16 13 and 14. And
that's it. John 163 and 14. Go ahead
when you get it.
>> Okay. John 16 and vers
uh 13 and 14 say,
"How be it, when he, the Spirit of
truth, is come, he will guide you into
all truth. For he shall not speak of
himself, but whatsoever he shall hear,
that shall he speak, and he will show
you things to come. He shall glorify me,
for he shall receive of mine and shall
show it unto you.
>> That's right. He shall receive of the
Lord and he will show it unto us and we
are to obey it.
That's all I got on that.
>> All right, thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question,
>> next one. Michelle from Louisiana asks,
"What is a Pauline Christian?" It was
mentioned in a Riverdale class at one
time.
>> Brother Dre, what is a Pauline
Christian?
>> First of all, you know, let's let's go
see something Paul said because
Paul
was a servant of Christ. Let's go to uh
1 Corinthians 11. We just going to read
verse one.
So Pauline Christian, let's look at
that.
Verse one. First Corinthians 11 and
verse one. Go ahead, brother James.
>> Be ye followers of me even as I also am
of Christ.
>> So he said, follow me as I follow
Christ.
He said, "Follow me as I follow Christ."
So, Pauline Christian.
Uh, I don't know about that. Let's go to
First Corinthians the first chapter now
and we going to look at something else
Paul said there. 1 Corinthians
the first chapter and read verse 10.
Now I beseech you, brethren, by the name
of our Lord Jesus Christ, that ye all
speak the same thing, and that there be
no divisions among you, but that ye be
perfectly joined together in the same
mind, and in the same judgment.
>> Now, skip down to verse 12 and continue.
Now this I say that every one of you
saith, I am of Paul and I am of Apollos
and I of Cphus and I of Christ.
>> Is Christ divided? Was Paul crucified
for you? Or were ye baptized in the name
of Paul?
>> The question is Pauline Christian we
talking about Christ not Paul. Paul
asked the question, "Was Paul crucified
for you? Was you baptized in the name of
Paul?" Now, what people tend to do is
they takes take Paul's writings and
twist them as Peter said in second Peter
the 3 chapter. Let's go read that and
that'll be it. Second Peter the 3
chapter 15 and 16.
Second Peter the 3 chapter vers
15 and 16 says an account that the
longsuffering of our Lord is salvation
even as our beloved brother Paul also
according to the wisdom given unto him
hath written unto you as also in all his
epistles speaking in them of these
things in which are some things hard to
be understood. good which they that are
unlearned and unstable rest as they do
also the other scriptures unto their own
destruction. So they take Paul's
writings and they put them over the
Lord's after they twist them because
Paul is not saying what they're saying.
Paul told you to follow him as he
followed Christ. Christ is the example,
not Paul. Christ is
and you follow what Paul is saying as he
follows Christ. That's all I got.
>> Say something.
>> Yes, sir.
>> I don't know where this person got that
terminology from, but I'm pretty sure
nobody in Riverdale used the
terminology. Pauline Christen.
>> Yeah. Yeah, whoever it is that as the
question, if you got the proof, somebody
use that terminology in the Israeli God
in Riverdale, please send us his name.
Thank you.
>> All right, hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next one.
>> Next one. Leaping Lamb asks, "Does God
or his angels speaks to individuals
today?
All right. Does God or his angels speak
to individuals today? Guest caller.
>> I don't know.
Answer that question.
>> All right. We leave it right there and
we move on to the next question.
>> Next question. Alex asks, "Do you all
have a message that explains or goes
into detail about lease in the kingdom
and how is the lake of fire and not a
status in the kingdom?"
>> All right, guess call them.
>> Okay, let's let's let's let's look at
the uh people that's going to be in the
kingdom. First, we're going to start
with what Jesus said after his
resurrection. Let's go into Matthew's
28th chapter and read verse 18.
>> Okay. Matthew 28 verse 18 says, "And
Jesus came and spake unto them, saying,
All power is given unto me in heaven and
in earth."
>> Now, all power
all means absolute. Isn't that correct?
>> Correct.
>> So if he had all power given to him in
heaven and earth, then what more did the
father have that he didn't have?
Nothing.
Now let's go in the Romans 8 chapter.
Read verses 14-1 17 and then we're going
to skip.
>> Okay. Romans 8 14-1 17 says, "For as
many as are led by the spirit of God,
they are the sons of God. For ye have
not received the spirit of bondage again
to fear, but ye have received the spirit
of adoption, whereby we cry, "Aba,
Father." The Spirit itself bears witness
with our spirit that we are the children
of God. And if children, then hes of God
and joint hes with Christ. If so be that
we suffer with him that we may be also
glorified together.
Now when you talking about joints with
Christ and Christ said all power in his
hand, if we are the children and if we
are glorified like him, have the same
type body when we change, then we on the
same level as he. Skip down to verse uh
uh 21
and read it.
>> Because the creature itself also shall
be delivered from the bondage of
corruption into the glorious liberty of
the children of God.
>> For we
>> how is this going to happen? Skip down
and read verse 23.
And not only they, but ourselves also,
which have the first fruits of the
spirit, even we ourselves grown within
ourselves, waiting for the adoption to
with the redemption of our body.
>> So if you going to be adopted into the
God family, that mean his body has got
to be redeemed. It cannot maintain its
flesh and blood status. Same type body
that Jesus have. Skip down verse 28 and
read verse 28 and 29.
>> And we know that all things work
together for good to them that love God,
to them who are the called according to
his purpose, for whom he did forno, he
also did predestinate to be conformed to
the image of his son, that he might be
the firstborn among many brethren.
So when we get this glorified body and
we adopted into God's family, then we
are just like Jesus. And Jesus is the
firstborn of many brethren. Now let me
see what the Lord said about this
firstborn of many brethren is first
begotten.
Go to Hebrews the first chapter and read
6-9.
>> Okay. Hebrews 1:es 6-9 says, "And again,
when he bringeth unto the first begotten
into the world, he saith, and let all
the angels of God worship him, and of
the angels,
>> we know that that's Jesus because he
said his firstborn of many brethren,
right?"
>> Yes.
>> So, he's the first begotten. That's like
in Hebrews
Romans the 8th chapter. But go ahead.
And of the angels he saith, who maketh
his angels spirits, and his ministers a
flame of fire?
But unto the Son he saith, Thy throne,
oh God, is forever and ever. A scepter
of righteousness is the scepter of thy
kingdom.
Thou has love.
>> What did he call?
>> What did he call it? Thy thy oh thy
throne, oh God, is forever and ever. A
scepter of righteousness is the scepter
of thy kingdom.
>> Because Jesus God didn't he
>> thou has loved righteousness and hated
iniquity. Therefore God, even thy God,
hath anointed thee with the oil of
gladness above thy fellows.
So God
Jesus have a father, he is God also,
isn't it? It's just like man
that's the son of man. His father his
father is man also. Isn't that correct?
>> Yes.
>> And we going to go to two more place and
it's going to be it. It's something that
Jesus uh uh uh requested. Let's go to
St. John 17 and we going to read verse
one and skip down and read verse five.
Okay. John 17 and1 verse says these
words spake Jesus and lifted up his eyes
to heaven and said father the hour come
glorify thy son that thy son also may
glorify thee.
Verse five says, "And now, oh father,
glorif glorify thou me with thine own
self with the glory which I had with
thee before the world was."
>> Okay. That's when he was in the form of
God, right?
>> Yes.
>> When he went
>> back to being God. So let's see what
happened when you're in the form of God.
The last place, Philippians 1, I'm
Philippians chapter 2 and read verse 5
and 6.
>> Okay.
Philippians
and Philippians 1 and verse 5 and 6.
>> Philippians 2.
>> Oh, okay. Philippians 2.
Verse five,
>> it says, "Let this mind be in you which
was also in Christ Jesus who who be who
talking to when he said, "Let this mind
be in you which is also in Christ
Jesus." Who is he talking to?
He's talking to us, mankind, the
servants of man of God. Lest this vine
be in you which is also in Christ Jesus.
Go ahead. who being in the form of God,
thought it not robbery to be equal with
God.
>> Who being in the form of God, thought it
not robbery to be equal with God. He
said, "Let this mind be in us." Didn't
Jesus say all power was given in his
hand?
>> God called him God, didn't he?
>> Yes, he did.
>> Now, if all if everybody if when you're
in the form of God, then you are equal
with God. Is this what we just read?
>> Yes.
>> So the only people in the God's kingdom
that's not equal is the people that's in
the lake of fire.
So they are the ones
that are least in the kingdom of God
because the whole kingdom is God.
There's a good fire that God of the
kingdom which everybody's God and they
are equal with God or either there's a
bad side of the kingdom where you are in
the lake of fire along with the fallen
angels.
>> So the question that was asked is who is
the least of kingdom? The people in the
lake of fire. Who is the greatest in the
kingdom?
Everybody that made the cut to being God
because they are equal. That's all I
have to say.
>> All right. And may all our viewers out
there strive to be equal with God. We
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one.
>> Next one. Brick Bratz says, "I
understand that during the Sabbath day,
we should not be lighting fires and
doing any labor." What else should we
not be doing to not pollute the Sabbath
day?
>> All right. No lighting a fire and doing
labor. And what else, brother Julius?
>> Let's go to Isaiah 58th chapter
in the 56th chapter at verse two. He
tell you, you got to keep the Sabbath
from polluting it, keeping his hand from
doing any evil.
You can't do no evil at all. Shouldn't
be doing it anyway. But Isaiah 58 and
13, James, one verse.
If thou turn away thy foot from the
Sabbath, from doing thy pleasure on my
holy day, and
>> you can't do your pleasure. You can't do
your pleasure. That mean you can't wash
your car. You can't wash your clothes.
You can't lay with your spouse cuz all
that is your pleasure.
Go ahead. and call the Sabbath a
delight, the holy of the Lord,
honorable,
and shall honor him, not doing thine own
ways,
>> not doing your own ways. It is the
Sabbath of the Lord. The Sabbath was
made for man, but the Sabbath is holy,
so you have to keep it holy by not
polluting it. You can't do your
pleasure. You can't do your own ways.
What else? nor finding thine own
pleasure.
>> No, you can't cook.
You can't cook. You can't barbecue.
Go ahead.
>> Nor speaking thine own words.
>> Even your conversation.
Even your conversation.
Let your conversation be about the Lord.
Meditation, prayer.
You, you know, uh not speaking thy own
words because it's the Lord. You got six
day to do all your labor and all your
work, but the Sabbath is the Lord. So,
we have to uh uh not do these things.
That's none of our pleasure or our ways
or our words. That's all I got.
>> All right. Lord say he rested on the
Sabbath day. Let's rest well. All right.
I hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one with a time
check.
>> Yes. Next one. The time is 8:07.
She also asked, "Can someone be born
with the righteous spirit even though
their parents, siblings, and relatives
have evil spirits?"
>> All right, guess call them the spirits.
>> Listen,
everybody's born the same. Go to Romans
the 7th chapter and read verse 14.
>> Romans 7 and verse 14 says,
For we know that the law is spiritual,
but I am carnal sold unto under sin.
>> Now, when you born, you're carnal, sold
under sin. And in order for you to have
a righteous spirit, as he said, then
that has to be developed through the
word of God and by keeping God's laws.
Just like becoming evil, you ain't born
evil. that have to be developed by you
breaking God's laws and continually and
will not repent
>> teach.
>> So we born the same ain't no spirit is
the spirit in this case is a mindset.
What kind of mindset can a baby have
you have to grow and develop into uh
your mind to serve good or to serve
evil? I think that's Romans the uh uh uh
uh which what's the last last verse in
that seventh chapter of Romans. Go read
that. Skip down to that.
>> I thank God through Jesus Christ our
Lord. So then with the mind I myself
serve the law of God but with the flesh
the law of sin.
>> So now when you with the flesh that mean
you start to want things that your flesh
is going for. You know your flesh call
for stealing somebody's money, sleep
with somebody's wife, or either you want
somebody you don't like a lying on them.
That have to be developed. Same thing
with the law of God. Keeping his
commandments, not stealing, not killing.
All of that stuff have to be taught to
you.
If you don't, then you if you are not
taught anything, then you will do
whatever your instinct call you. So
ain't nobody born with a good spirit in
them or a bad or evil spirit in them.
You're born with a mind which God
develops with his word or either which
Satan deceives with his antics.
>> Yes.
>> That's all I have to say.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Right. I hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
>> Next one. The Bora Walder says, "Please
explain First Kings 10 verses 8 and 9
and First Kings 12 verse 4. What
happened
with what Queen Sheba saw with King
Solomon and Solomon making Israel yoke
grievous and heavy yoke.
All right. Got a little bit in that
question there, brother Julius.
>> Yes. Uh, we're talking two different
people. The first part of your question
is
about Solomon and the Queen of Sheba.
She came to hear about the wisdom of
Solomon that God gave to him. Not to
sleep with him, but to hear the wisdom
that God put up on him. The second part
of your question is not Solomon. Well,
let's go to the first part and read it.
First Kings 10 8-9.
Hold on a minute. Hold on a minute. Pick
up at verse one.
>> Okay.
>> First Kings 10 and1.
>> And when the Queen of Sheba heard of the
fame of Solomon concerning the name of
the Lord, she came to prove him with
hard questions.
>> Man, and verse three. And Solomon told
her all her questions. There was not
anything hid from the king which he told
her not.
>> Verse six.
>> And she said to the king, it is with it
was a true report that I heard in mine
own land of thy acts and of thy wisdom.
>> That's what she came to hear from
Solomon. Now skip down. And when she saw
that and Solomon answered all her
questions and she noticed that how what
he was surrounded with and the joy of
his men and his servants. Verse eight,
>> happy are thy men. Happy are these thy
servants which stand continually before
thee and that hear thy wisdom
>> because it is a wonderful and it's a
pleasure to hear the wisdom of God and
the knowledge of God. Verse N.
>> Blessed be the Lord thy God, which
delighted in thee to set thee on the
throne of Israel, because the Lord loved
Israel forever. Therefore made he thee
king to do judgment and justice.
>> Because Solomon told her that. Now let's
go to the second part of your question.
Let's go to first Kings the 12th
chapter. Solomon died. Now
first Kings chapter 12 now his son Rehab
not Solomon Rihaboam is reigning now or
uh uh it's raining. Go ahead verse one.
>> And Riaboam went to Shisham. And for all
Israel were come to Shikim to make him
king.
>> Now
Sodom Riabom asked the question. Skip
down to verse four and go ahead. Thy
father made our yoke grievous. Now
therefore make thou the grievous service
of thy father and his heavy yoke which
he put upon us lighter and we will serve
thee.
>> But Solomon didn't listen. Uh he went to
uh the counselors that was on didn't
listen.
>> Ria Boam didn't listen. He went to the
uh Solomon's counselors and look what
she they told him. Look what they told
him. Look, uh, verse seven, go ahead.
>> And they spake unto him, saying, If thou
will be a servant unto this people this
day, and will serve them, and answer
them, and speak good words to them, then
they will be thy servants forever.
>> So, a wise king rules righteous, and he
is a servant of the people, and he rules
for a long time. But Solom but Riaboam
didn't listen to Solomon's counsel. Look
what he did at verse 8.
>> But he forsook the counsel of the old
men which they had given him and
consulted with the young men that were
grown up with him and which stood before
him.
>> So now they so look how they look how
they counted him. Verse 11 and that's
it.
And now, whereas my father did laid you
with a heavy yoke, I will add to your
yoke. My father has chastised you with
whips, but I will chastise you with
scorpions.
>> In other words, I'm going to oppress you
more. Instead of listening to the older
men that came up with Solomon, he listen
to the young men that came up with him.
And eventually he ruled the people uh
wickedly because
the kingdom was divided after Solomon's
death. That's all I got. You can read
the whole story on your own.
>> Yeah.
>> So one story one story is about Solomon
and the Queen of Sheba. The other one is
about Riabom taking foolish counsel from
his young men from the men that grew up
with him.
>> Yeah. Should have listened to old
school.
>> Yep.
All right, we're gonna move on to our
next question.
>> Next question. Ran 64 asks in Isaiah 34,
excuse me, in Isaiah 13
19-22,
which Babylon is these scriptures
talking about? Some people say this is
America.
>> All right, brother Jerome.
Well, um, according to what we read out
of the Bible, it's referring to what's
called Babylon the Great. Okay. Uh,
that's really what it's referring to.
It's not actually referring to America.
Okay. But let's go to uh that Isaiah 13.
>> Okay. Isaiah 13 and9 says, "And Babylon,
the glory of kingdoms, the beauty of the
cales excellency shall be as when God
overthrew Sodom and Gomorra. It shall
never be inhabited, neither shall it be
dwelt in from generation to generation.
Neither shall the Arabian
pitch tent there. Neither shall the
shepherds make their fold there. But
wild beasts of the desert shall lie
there and their houses shall be full of
joyful creatures and owls shall dwell
there and sats shall dance there.
>> Yeah. So this
>> this is future u prophecy. But let's
let's go to uh the first verse of the
same chapter. We going to do some
skipping throughout this chapter, uh,
James, to try to explain why it's
Babylon the great. Okay, so read verse
one, then we going to skip to verse six.
>> The burden of Babylon which Isaiah the
son of Amos did see.
>> Skip to verse six.
>> How ye, for the day of the Lord is at
hand. It shall come as a destruction
from the Almighty.
>> This is a future event. Skip and read
verse 9 through 12.
Behold, the day of the Lord cometh
cruel, both with wrath and fierce anger,
to lay the land desolate, and he shall
destroy the sinners thereof out of it.
>> Yeah, by this time he going to be
dealing with Babylon a great. Okay, go
ahead and read.
>> For the stars of heaven and the and the
constellations thereof shall not give
their light. The sun shall be darkened
in his going forth and the moon shall
not cause her light to shine.
>> Yeah, that's uh a tag that show you in
you in the great tribulation.
>> Go ahead.
>> And I will punish the world for their
evil and the wicked for their iniquity.
And I will cause the arrogancy of the
proud to cease and will lay low the
haltiness of the terrible. Mhm.
>> I will make a man more precious than
fine gold. Even a man than even a man
than the golden wedge of.
>> Yeah. Cuz
the Lord going to destroy
from one end of the earth to the other.
But uh skip down to verse 17, read to
the 19.
>> Behold, I will stir up the me against
them, which shall not regard silver. And
as for gold, they shall not delight in
it.
>> The Russians are uh the that's who the
mey mess are in this verse. They the
Russians and he going to bring them
against Babylon the great which a which
is a a conglomerate of of nations uh uh
which is dealing with Western Europe.
Okay.
Go ahead. Their bowls also shall dash
the young men to pieces. And they shall
have no pity on the fruit of the womb.
Their eyes shall not spare children.
And Babylon, the glory of kingdoms, the
beauty of the called excellency shall be
as when God overthrew Sodom and Gomorra.
>> Yeah. So he going to destroy Babylon the
great. He said Babylon is fallen. It's
fallen. That's what it say in
Revelations. That's all I got on it.
>> All right, thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question,
>> next question. Be alert ask, is it wrong
to allow a Sunday worshipper to pray for
you?
>> Let's open this up to the panel. Is it
wrong to allow a Sunday worshipper to
pray for you?
>> Let's go uh let's examine this a little
bit.
Go read quick where
uh Paul said who did Paul said that the
Gentiles uh uh
>> sacrifice
>> sacrifice.
>> All right.
Search mode for that.
>> That's 1 Corinthians 10 and 20.
>> Okay. 1 Corinthians 10 and verse 20
says,
"But I say that the things which the
Gentiles sacrifice, they sacrifice to
devils and not to God. And I would not
that ye should have fellowship with
devils."
>> Now he said the Gentiles, that correct?
>> Yes.
>> Now let's
>> let's show you. And so now,
uh, the first message that Mary got
that she was going to have a son, it
said that he was going to sit on David's
throne. Let's look the first chapter.
>> Luke the first chapter and start reading
at verse 30.
>> Okay. Luke 1:30 says, "And the angel
said unto her, Fear not, Mary, for thou
has found favor with God. And behold,
thou shalt conceive in thy womb, and
bring forth a son, and shalt call his
name Jesus. He shall be great, and shall
be called the Son of the Highest. And
the Lord God shall give unto him the
throne of his father David.
and he shall and he shall reign over the
house of Jacob forever and his kingdom
there shall be no end.
>> Now that mean that he's going to rule on
earth. Isn't it correct?
>> Right.
>> Yes.
>> Revelation the 5th chapter. It starts
where uh uh when Jesus opened up the
seal the people said uh uh they made
them kings made them kings and priests.
This is in when Jesus come and where
they going to rule at. Okay, that's
Revelation 10 or do 10 and uh I mean I'm
sorry five and 10 or do you want me to
back up uh a verse?
>> Back up a verse or nine. Okay, it says,
"And they sung a new song, saying, Thou
art worthy to take the book, and to open
the seals thereof, for thou was slain,
and has redeemed us to God by thy blood
out of every kindred and tongue and
people and nation, and has made us unto
our God, kings, and priests, and we
shall reign on the earth." Mhm.
>> Now, these are the servants of God that
is going to rain on the earth. One other
two other places. And let's go into
Revelation 21st chapter start at verse
one.
>> Okay. Revelation 21 and one says, "And I
saw a new heaven and a new earth, for
the first heaven and the first earth
were passed away, and there was no more
sea.
And I saw And I, John, saw the holy
city, New Jerusalem, coming down from
God out of heaven, prepared as a bride
adorned for her husband.
And I heard a great And I heard a great
voice out of heaven, saying, "Behold,
the tabernacle of God is with men, and
he will dwell with them, and they shall
be his people, and God himself shall be
with them, and be their God."
So now Jesus is coming to the earth. The
father is coming to the earth
and the kingdom is going to be on earth.
Both of them tell you in the 20th
chapter of revelation that the Lord is
going to rule this earth for a thousand
years. And we and we going to help him
rule this earth for a thousand years.
Now let's see who wants to go to heaven.
Let's go into uh Isaiah the 14th
chapter. Start reading at verse 12.
>> Okay. Isaiah 14 and 12 says,
"How art thou fallen from heaven, oh
Lucifer, son of the morning? How art
thou cut down to the ground which didest
weaken the nations. For thou hast said
in thine heart, I will ascend into
heaven, and I will exalt my throne above
the stars of God. I will sit also upon
the mount of the congregation in the
sides of the north. I will ascend above
the heights of the clouds. I will be
like the most high.
Now that's Satan. Lucifer, he said he
going to go to heaven. Isn't that
correct?
>> Right.
>> Yes.
>> All the gods. People said they going to
come to earth. And did we read where you
say you cannot partake of the table of
devils and of the table of and also of
the table of God?
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
>> Now let's give me an example how you
cannot and what will happen to you. Go
into Genesis
third chapter
and this is when man had eaten of the
tree of knowledge and good and evil that
God told him not to. Start reading at
verse 20.
>> Okay. Genesis 3 verse 20 says, "And Adam
called his wife's name Eve, because she
was the mother of all living. Unto Adam
also and to his wife did the Lord make
coats of skin and clothe them. And the
Lord God said, Behold, the man has
become as one of us to know good and
evil. And now le he put forth his hand
and take also of the tree of life and
eat and live forever.
There therefore therefore the Lord God
sent him forth from the garden of Eden
to till the ground from whence he was
taken. So, so he drove out the man and
he placed at the east of the garden of
Eden cherubims and a flaming swore
turned every way to keep the way of the
tree of life.
Now, why did he drive him out? Because
he had partake of the table of sat
Satan. Adam and Eve had so he drove him
out. You ain't ready to be a be God yet.
Then again too, the Lord say he going he
want to come to earth. states he want to
go to heaven. The Lord said the seventh
day
is his Sabbath day. It's a sign between
him and his people, not the first day.
So now I just put that out there cuz I
want you to answer your own question.
Should you allow
a minister, a person that's following
what it was Sunday, going to heaven,
eating anything,
pray over you.
You make the decision yourself. That's
all I have to say.
>> All right. As we move on to our next
question.
Next question. Michelle from Louisiana
asks, "May I get the correct
understanding of a juror in 2 Chronicles
18 verse 15? And is this the same that
was spoken to a fake rabbi years ago?"
>> All right. Why don't we go to that uh 2
Chronicles 18 and 15
and they want to know about the word
adjour.
Okay,
>> go ahead. The guest caller will take it
from there.
Uh 2 2 Chronicles 18-15 says, "And the
king said to him, how many times shall I
adjure thee that thou say nothing but
the truth to me in the name of the
Lord?"
Now, you know, the word adjour have
several meanings,
but I'm pretty sure
that the word uh uh when it was used uh
like he have written down there as as
what as what brother said to the fake
rabbi,
I'm pretty sure he used the definition
that said that uh uh uh uh I appeal to
your honesty.
In other words, I appeal to your honesty
in the word of God
that you answer this question that I'm
asking you.
So would you have several words? I
appeal to you to you honestly. Sometime
like when you when we use it when uh uh
uh uh uh when king uh uh uh Ahab used
this prophet that came and told him go
up and prosper, he said how many time
must I jewel you? Now in his case is how
many time must I command you but before
you oh tell me nothing but what the Lord
said. Well, you'll have a lot of
sometime appeal to you honestly. You
know, I'm appealing to you to honestly
come clean with me. Sometime I'm
commanding you.
>> Yeah. Another definition, another
definition to strongly urge. I strongly
urge you to tell me.
>> Yeah, that's right. See, there's several
of them that's through that. So, so
brother B was in no position to command
this Edomite rabbi. So what he did, he
appealed to him
and he strongly urged him to come clean
with me.
It worked cuz he came clean with him.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
>> Next one. humility says. So the question
asked last week about Joseph two fathers
one in Matthew and the other in late in
Luke third chapter humility says I read
both and Jacob would be his biological
and he lie his father-in-law correct
>> last time you asked this question and it
was told by the guest caller that We
don't know.
And that answer still remains the same.
Guest caller.
>> It still remain the same.
>> All right. And we're going to leave it
right there, Sister Deborah, because we
getting ready to go into new territory.
Right.
>> Yes. We are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday, July the 23rd, 2025.
Alex Williams asks in Leviticus 23
verse1 17,
why do they start back using leaven?
>> All right. Why do they start back using
leaven, brother Jerome?
>> Let's go read it.
>> Okay. 23:17.
It says, "Ye shall bring out of your
habitations two wave loaves of two tenth
deals. They shall be of fine flour and
they shall be baked with leaven. They
are the first fruits unto the Lord."
Okay,
this is actually talking about the uh
the Pentecost.
It's not talking about the feast of
unleaven bread where you have to get the
leavenvening out your house and how you
not supposed to eat unleaven bread for
seven days. That's the feast of unleaven
bread. But the verse you are asking
about that's talking about uh the
Pentecost. Okay. And so uh let's let's
read verse 15
through 17.
>> Okay.
And ye shall count unto you from the
moral after the Sabbath, from the day
that you were brought the sheath of the
wave offering, seven Sabbaths shall be
complete.
>> That's 49 days. And then you got one
more day, which is Go ahead and read.
>> Even until the tomorrow after the
seventh Sabbath shall ye number 50 days,
and ye shall
>> And ye shall offer a new meat offering
unto the Lord.
>> Uhhuh. Ye shall bring it out of your
habitations two wave loaves of two tenth
deals. They shall be of fine flour. They
shall be baked with leaven. They are the
first fruits unto the Lord. Okay? And
what that's referring to is us because
it's referring to those that's going to
uh uh come up in the first resurrection.
And it's this this offering is baked
with leaven cuz we have sin in us. Okay,
it's covered by the blood of Jesus if if
if we overcome. Okay, and Jesus was the
uh first fruit that was offered. And
then there's another offering that's
made on Pentecost which represent us and
we got sin at us. The Lord don't. Okay.
So this time talking about Pentecost.
That's all I got.
>> All right. Thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question,
>> moving on. Michelle from Louisiana asks,
"Is there any way to get a mentor for
scripture help from IOG?"
Because I don't trust anyone but an IOG
teacher.
>> All right. Actually, she gets some help
all the way in Louisiana. Brother Dre,
what you say?
>> Say you should continue to watch the the
uh Q&A and attend Bible class and come
keep the Sabbath day and if you have
questions afterwards, you know, put them
in the Q&A or talk to the minister at
that particular class. But, uh, let's
go. And as far as trusting, because to
mentor means to to have an experienced
trusted advisor.
The word of God is what we trust and we
are advised by. Let's go to Proverbs 3
and read verses five and six. Proverbs 5
and six. when you get it.
>> Three and verse 5 and six says, "Trust
in the Lord with all thine heart and
lean not unto thine own understanding.
In all thy ways acknowledge him, and he
shall direct thy paths."
>> So the word of God is what directs our
paths and what we trust in. So continue.
You you came up on a blessing and coming
to the Israel of God. continue to study
and and ask questions and attend lessons
and look at lessons online. Uh one more
place, let's go to second Timothy 2 and
we're going to read verse 15. Second
Timothy 2 and 15.
>> Go ahead.
>> Second Timothy 2 and 15.
Mhm.
>> It says, "Study to show thyself approved
unto God, a workman that needeth not to
be ashamed, rightly dividing the word of
truth."
>> That's it right there. So, you you are
uh asking questions on Q&A, prayerfully,
you attending a class, ag
and and uh you continue to grow. That's
all I got. Right. Yes, sir. Pray for
understanding along the way. Yes, sir.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
>> next one. Edward Barber says, "I would
like to know if Solomon repented before
he died."
>> Uh, let's see what the book say.
First Kings 11.
First Kings 11. cuz
I haven't seen it written in this book
we going in first Kings 11
read verse six verse four first brother
go ahead for it came to pass when
Solomon was old that his wives turned
away his heart from other gods and his
heart was not perfect with the Lord his
God as was the heart of David his father
>> verse six And Solomon did evil in the
sight of the Lord, and went not fully
after the Lord, as did David his father.
>> Verse 9.
>> And the Lord was angry with Solomon,
because his heart was turned from the
Lord God of Israel, which had appeared
unto him twice.
>> Yep. Got the kingdom split. Read 42 and
43. And let's see if it say anything
about repenting here. Go ahead.
And the time that Solomon reigned in
Jerusalem over all Israel was 40 years.
And Solomon slept with his fathers and
was buried in the city of David his
father. And Rahaboam his son reigned in
his steed.
>> So it don't say there that he repented.
We hope so, but it doesn't say it there.
Anybody else?
It didn't say that he didn't repent. So,
we have to leave it alone, don't we?
>> That's right.
>> Yeah. Didn't say he did or did not. So,
>> we know he was the wisest man who ever
lived. We know he wrote uh Proverbs. We
know he wrote uh uh Ecclesiastes. We
know he wrote Songs of Solomon.
>> So,
that's work right there. But we don't
know.
>> Yep. We are spreading that word also
throughout the whole world.
All right,
next question.
>> Next question. Charlotte W asks, "Why
are there few teachings and lessons on
true repentance?
And does God forgive when we say first
John 1 verse 9 and Psalms 51?"
>> All right. Well, we'll open it up to the
panel, but when you get some wisdom, you
understand a lot of lessons that deal
with repentance and how you should act
when you married and how the children
should act and what you have to do to
work out your own salvation with fear
and trembling. Let's go to first John 1
and9 and then let's open it up to the
panel also with that Psalms. We're not
going to read the whole chapter of 51.
Let's go to that first uh first John 1:9
and then go ahead with the question
again sister Deborah and we open it up
to the panel.
>> Okay. It says if we confess our sins he
is faithful and just to forgive us our
sins and to cleanse us from all
unrighteousness.
3:10
>> If we say that we have not sinned, we
make him a liar and his word is not with
us.
>> Right? Cuz the Lord said, "All have
sinned and come short of the glory of
God." Open to the pastor.
>> Yeah. Could I say something?
>> Um,
>> yeah.
>> You might not hear it in just one Israel
of God. We got a whole lot of churches,
whole lot of Israel of God. You got
brothers who teach on different subject
matters. You just got to search it out.
But the whole Bible tells you about
repent from the Old Testament to the New
Testament. Repent. Repent. So it doesn't
have to necessarily be in someone's
particular lesson. But it is written if
you do the reading the uh it is written
all over the book. Repent. Even Peter
told you repent. Don't let sin be your
ruin. Ezekiel the 18th chapter tell you
you just got to go out there and read
it. It doesn't necessarily have to be in
a lesson all the time, you know, because
I know at the end of the God
headquarters, we teach a lot of it.
>> Yeah. Whenever we do a lesson on
baptism, we we definitely going to quote
that Acts the 2nd chapter verse 36, 37
and maybe even 38 where he tell you to
repent and be baptized every one of you
in the name of Jesus Christ for the
remission of sins and you shall receive
the gift of the Holy Ghost.
>> Exactly. And the Bible is so vast and
there's so many subject matters to deal
with, we just can't single it down to
one. That's why we teach by subject and
title.
>> And if you look at David in in Psalm 51,
he starts that off with crying out to
the Lord for mercy and asking to be
cleansed of his iniquity and from his
sin. and he acknowledging his sins and
the Lord
>> he put something on David but he did not
give David the judgment that was due for
the sin that he
>> yeah and like you said about washing
from those sins
let's go they made mention about Psalms
51 let's go there James and read one and
two what Dre was saying also about you
know wash me thoroughly
>> okay Psalm 51 and verse 1 and 2 says,
"Have mercy upon me, oh God, according
to thy loving kindness according unto
the multitude of thy tender mercies.
Blot out my transgressions.
>> Wash me thoroughly from mine iniquity,
and cleanse me from my sin."
>> Yep.
>> Read verse 10. Read verse 10, brother.
>> Yep. Create in me a clean heart, oh God,
and renew a right spirit within me.
>> Yeah.
>> So, uh they want to know, does God
forgive when you read these scriptures?
>> Oh, of course. The whole thing is if you
truly repent, confess your sins to your
God, he will hear and he will forgive.
Let's give a perfect example. Let's go
into Luke the 23rd chapter and read from
verse 39 to 43.
>> Luke the 23rd chapter 49.
>> No, verse 39 to 43.
>> Oh, 39. Okay. It says, "And one of the
malfactors which were hanged railed on
him, saying, If thou be the Christ, save
thyself and us." But the other answer
and rebuked him, saying, "Does not thou
fear God, seeing thou art in the same
condemnation?"
And we indeed justly, for we receive the
due reward of our deeds. But this man
had done nothing a miss.
And he said unto Jesus,"Lord,
remember me when thou comest into thy
kingdom." And Jesus said unto him,
"Verily I say unto thee, today shalt
thou be with me in paradise."
>> Now this man repented
and he confessed his sins where he say
we belong where we are because of what
we did.
>> But this man has done nothing. Then he
turned around and he made a request
because that's what you do when you're
praying.
>> God, remember me when thou comest into
thy kingdom.
>> And he said, I'm saying unto you today,
you shall be with me in paradise. So he
confessed his sin on the last day of his
life. And in order for do that, he had
to repent. And he prayed to the Lord to
remember me. In other words, forgive me.
And the Lord tell him, I'm going to
remember you cuz you going to be in the
first resurrection. Of course he hear
you if you repent and it's genuine and
you confess to him that you have been a
sinner.
That's
>> right. Yeah. Well, you sit on the mercy
seat
>> and and on your own, please read Isaiah
55 and 7. Lord said that he would
abundantly pardon if the wicked forsake
his way and the unrighteous man his
thoughts and return.
He will have mercy and he will
abundantly pardon.
>> Yeah. What's grip?
>> That's Isaiah 55 and seven.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. because she did states, "Is that
just enough just reading the scripture?"
And no, you can't just read the
scripture. You have to repent.
>> Absolutely.
>> Change your ways and and and make sure
you walking in what you read.
>> That's it.
>> All right. Thank you for that question.
as we move on to our next question.
While time is a ticking, Deborah.
>> Yes, next question. Charles Tumer uh
asks, "Is it okay for me and my wife to
get ma remarried again after being
baptized? We are currently married
still, but we were not married with this
knowledge of the truth."
>> All right. They want to know about
getting remarried because they had
baptized now they want to get remarried.
Guess call them.
>> If they want to, why not?
>> Yep. Choice is yours.
>> All right. We're going to move on to our
next question.
>> Next question. The words of spirit says
if the evil angels are under chains of
darkness
then what actually happened during
Christ's temptation?
Did Satan really appear to Jesus or was
Jesus just babbling thoughts in his
mind?
He appeared unto the Lord.
Not in his mind because it doesn't say
that. But let's go into let's go into
Luke 4 because the one that he appeared
before was the same one that created
him.
But let's go into Luke 4
and let's pick it up brother at that
verse one. Go ahead.
>> And Jesus being full of the Holy Ghost
returned from Jordan and was led by the
spirit into the wilderness.
>> Was led by the spirit. It says nothing
about being in his mind here in verse
three. Go ahead.
And the devil said unto him, "If thou be
the son of God, command this stone that
it be made bread."
>> Yep. Skip down to verse six.
>> And the devil said unto him, "All this
power will I give thee, and the glory of
them, for that is delivered unto me, and
to whomsoever I will give it." Mhm.
>> If thou if thou therefore will worship
me, all shall be thine.
And Jesus answered and said unto him,
Get thee behind me, Satan. For it is
written, Thou shalt worship the Lord thy
God, and him only shalt thou serve.
>> Yep. And when he was through with the
temptation, what happened in verse uh
13?
And when the devil had ended all the
temptation, he departed from him for a
season.
>> Departed from him, not from his mind.
Departed from him.
>> 14.
>> And Jesus returned into the power of the
spirit into Galilee. And there went out
a fame of him through all the region
round about.
>> Yep. So, hey, he didn't have to he
wasn't under chains of darkness when it
came to Jesus. Open to the panel.
>> Listen,
Jesus had to have the exact same
temptation that Adam and Eve had.
>> Mhm.
>> God was in the Garden of Eden and they
could see him. The reason is because
when they heard his voice as he was
walking in the garden, they hid him hid
themselves.
>> They could see him. he could see them.
Now, how is it that Jesus going to come
and endure and don't endure the same
temptation that man did? Cuz in the
judgment, and he's the judge, man said,
"Look, he didn't pop up in front of you
like he popped up in front of us."
>> Mhm.
>> Had he had he uh done it like that, then
you would have went the same way. So he
had to be physically
looking at g at the devil and the devil
physically looking and talking with him
because that's where it was in the
garden of Eden with Adam and Eve because
he had the same temptation that man did.
That's
>> right. Yep. Cuz he he even said in
Hebrews 4:15 that he was tempted in all
points just like we were.
>> That's it.
All right, we hope that that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one.
>> Next one. Wicked wicked creation asks,
"What do you have to do to become a
teacher of God's word? Besides being
between 30 and 50 years old, male, and
baptized, do you have to go to school or
be ordained?
Yes, caller. What's the requirements?
>> First retirement, are you right? Between
uh uh 30 and 50. Second thing is is you
read the Bible and you pray to God. If
he wants you to become a teacher, then
you will become a teacher.
>> Then you gonna go to school. What
school,
brother Bo, that that the Lord used to
start the Israel of God went to nobody
school.
He studied no theology.
He sat on a man that taught the word and
he read the Bible and prayed to the Lord
to give him wisdom, knowledge, and
understanding.
And when he had gotten where the Lord
thought he was ready, the Lord
dispatched him.
So what school you going to go to? Your
school is from Genesis to Revelation.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right.
Okay. We're moving on to our next
question.
>> Uh next question. In Galatians 5 verse
10, why does Paul say a person should
bear judgment?
for telling someone to be circumcised.
>> So, let's go to the regulations.
>> Yeah, it's really been removed that
question.
>> Oh, it's been removed.
>> Read it.
>> Okay. Galatians 5:10 says, "I have
confidence in you through the Lord, that
ye will be none otherwise minded, but he
that troubleth you shall bear his
judgment whosoever he be."
>> Now I'm concerned the circumcision. You
know what I said to the person that
asked this question?
>> As soon as you see Paul, ask him.
All right, we're gonna leave it right
there as we move on to our next question
as time is ticking.
Uh yes, this other question from
Michelle has been removed also. But it
uh the question was
uh Michelle from Louisiana says, "My
sister in Christ at work as for
understanding for Revelations 12
verse14."
All right, brother Julius, can you uh
shed some light on that Revelation 12
and 14 right quick?
>> Yes. In a nutshell, this woman
metaphorically speaking is Israel
escaping to the wilderness where she is
protected by the Lord for three and a
half years during the great tribulation.
>> Yep.
The place to be when you got
>> wisdom, knowledge, and understanding to
flee to that wilderness. Thank you for
that, brother. We're going to move on to
our next question.
>> Yes, and this one has been removed too.
Just no chill as when people use a
translation version of the Bible like
NLV,
etc.
Uh are they
all right? The question has been
removed.
>> So I'm moving on with that. If you can
read,
>> I can answer the question.
>> Okay. Hold on.
>> Yeah, hold on one second, Deborah.
Because the reason this question is
important because there are a lot of
different versions of the Bible out here
>> and everybody likes to stand on what
they believe in. So, let's let our
brother share on it and
>> right. So, could you read the question
because I no longer have it. Read the
question, please. So, brother Julius, it
say when people use a translated version
of the Bible like the NLT or the NLV or
the RSV,
etc., and all the other Bibles out
there, are they adding to and taking
away from the word of God according to
that? Revelations 22 and verse 18 and
19.
>> Let's go to read that real quick, James,
and let's answer this.
>> Okay. Revelation 22 and 18 and 19 says,
"For I for I testify unto every man that
heareth the words of the prophecy of
this book. If any man shall add unto
these things, God shall add unto him the
plagues that are written in this book.
And if any man shall take away from the
words of this book of the of this
prophecy, God shall take away his part
out of the book of life and out of the
holy city from the things which are
written in this book.
So the answer is yes. They are adding
and taking away from and because they
are all these versions or translations
are predicated off of the KJV. I'mma
give you a a an example. Let's go to
Genesis, I'm sorry, Genesis 2 and 7.
>> Okay?
>> And you might want to get your Bible app
uh on your phone or if you have a New
World Translation, which is a Jehovah
Witness Bible. What do it say in the
King James? Genesis 2:7. And the Lord
God formed man of the dust of the ground
and breathed into his nostrils the
breath of life and man became a living
soul.
>> So man became a living soul. Now in the
New World Translation, the NWT and in
the New King James Version, it says man
became a living being.
Okay? So now a soul is a body.
Now, let's go to Matthew the 17th
chapter. And somebody you could Google
this on your own or you can look it up
or if you have a New International
Version, NIV,
let's read Matthew the 17th chapter.
>> Okay?
>> Matthew the 17th chapter
in the KJV. Read Matthew the 17th
chapter and read verse 21.
How be it this kind goeth not out by
prayer and fasting.
How be it this kind go out not by uh
prayer or fasting. Now in the NIV,
guess what? Verse 21 is missing.
It's totally missing.
But in the KJV there is a verse 21.
But in the NIV it jump
it it jumps be from 20 verse 20 and then
it goes right to 22.
All that is missing.
So the Lord said don't add or take away.
You got to the New King James Version
got at least maybe 3,000 changes in it.
Mhm.
>> So you have when you take away from the
word of God, you change what God is
saying, you change the meaning of the
verse or the chapter.
So that's why he say you don't add or
you don't take away because he knew man
was going to come up with these
versions. We use the KJV because it is
commissioned by God and backed up by
history. It is a proven book. all these
other transl and they all start with uh
in the beginning God because they're
predicated off of the KJV but they take
words out of it and they add stuff to it
just like the Lord said they would do so
war I
like to say this why is it that you
going to get a book
and go in it and upgrade it and why
should I listen to a upgraded book when
I should can go to the book that you use
to upgrade
and teach me.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Not like they went back to the original
language and and and and brought it up
from the ground. They got a King James
version and they upgraded it. Okay.
>> And yes, they adding to it and they
taking away from it. And Revelation tell
you 22 tell you what's going to happen
to you. That's all I have to say.
>> That's right. And for the Old Testament
Christians in that Deuteronomy the 4th
chapter and verse two it say ye shall
not add unto the word which I command
you neither shall ye diminish thought
from it that you may keep the
commandments of the Lord your God which
I command you.
>> And the book says Jesus Christ the same
today, yesterday and forever. And
another scripture he tell you he changes
not. I am the Lord and I change not. So
you don't have the right to change his
words.
>> That's right. King James, all you need
to get salvation and that crown of
everlasting life. Sister Deborah,
>> brother Cornell always say no other
version or no other book will be
tolerated on this platform.
>> That's correct, brother. That is
correct. So sister Deborah, let's go to
our final question of the evening.
All right, that will be Pauline R asks
in Jeremiah 50 verse8.
What does this mean? Who are the called
deings?
>> Jeremiah 50 and verse 8. Let's go there,
brother.
>> Okay. Jeremiah 50 and verse8 says,
"Remove out of the midst of Babylon and
go forth out of the land of the calans
and be as the hegoats before the
flocks."
>> Who is the called panel?
>> He said those are the Babylonians.
>> And the Babylonians are the children of
Japat.
And the children of Japat are Gentiles.
>> Yes, sir. recall
are white folks.
>> Yeah.
>> Babylonic
that is talking about the European
Union. White folks,
the children and the first Gentile that
ruled this earth were the Babylonians or
or they was called the called. So they
are the Gentiles. white folks come out
from among them first first spiritually
by not dealing with this uh uh uh uh uh
teaching that they got because the gent
white folks are gentile and Paul told
you that uh Gentiles sacrifice the
devils first you come out of her by
coming out of this bad doctrine
>> y
>> and when it's time to flee you got to
come out of her physically and go to the
wilderness that's all I have to say
>> all All right. And what a fine question
to end our evening on. And we want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who tuned in with us and sent in
those questions. We want to thank you.
And we have ran out of time. But if you
submitted a question, we didn't get to
it. Please don't resubmit it because
Deborah take your original question and
put it in rotation and we will deal with
that question next week. So until we all
come together again, we ask you to be
safe. Be blessed. Stay prayed up. And
may the Lord have mercy on us all as
brother James closes us out.
>> Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven. Give us this day our daily
bread, and forgive us our debts as we
forgive our debtors. and lead us not
into temptation, but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen.